Guide to the Stephen Harmon Photographs 1942, 1968-2017 PR 362
New-York Historical Society
- Series P.I. Photographic Prints, 1942, 1970s-2011; 1.5 Linear feet in 1 flat box and 1 flat file folder
  - 10 color photographs, 8-1/2 x 11 in., Various subjects, 1970-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes subway car with graffiti, Flatiron Building, Charles Scribners & Sons storefront, phone booths, pretzel wagon, P&G Bar neon lights, and an abortion rights demonstration. Gift, 2012.
  - 31 color photographs, 8-1/2 x 11 in., Various subjects, 1970s-2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes, among others, Amsterdam Restaurant, Blarney Stone restaurant, Chinatown, World Trade Center, Camel cigarette sign in Times Square, Village Cigars in Greenwich Village, Grand Central Station 42nd Steet entrance, various store signage, New York State Supreme Courthouse, 72nd Street subway station (interior), views of Manhattan skyline from #7 train, and Elmhurst gas tanks along the Long Island Expressway. All are signed. Most are titled on back.
  - 8 color photographs, 16 x 20 in. New York City scenes., 1983 (Folder FF-1)
    Brownstone building stoops on 82nd off Amsterdam, with graffiti; Antonio's barber shop on Amsterdam and 82nd; P&G Cafe/Bar on northeast corner of Amsterdam & 73rd; network of fire escapes on a building on Bleecker Street; fireworks over the Brooklyn Bridge on its 100th anniversary; 3 wintry street scenes (at Broadway & 72nd (2 views) and at West End & 72nd). All signed. Gift, 1983.
  - Ephemera. 1 wedding invitation card, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Invitation from Mr & Mrs. Max Markman and Mr & Mrs. Samuel Eisenkop to the marriage of their children Eleanor and Hyman (the parents of Stephen Harmon) at Temple Bnai Mordechai, Brooklyn. Gift, February 2019.